Normandy Real

Frontend Developer, Database Administrator

normandy.real@gmail.com

Summary

I'm a mainframe professional with over 12 years of software engineering and 5 years of database administration experience. With a keen interest in modern web and related technologies, I completed Udacity's Front-end Developer Nanodegree Program. Using the practical experience from the program and my strong technical background in software development, I am exploring opportunities to shift into a frontend engineer. I'm a fast and eager learner and works well alone or with a team.

Experience

Lead Consultant at NCS Pte Ltd

October 2007 - Present (7 years 8 months)

IT Consultant at A-IT Software Services Pte Ltd

July 2005 - October 2007 (2 years 4 months)

Team Lead at Accenture

September 2001 - July 2005 (3 years 11 months)

Skills & Expertise

SDLC

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

AJAX

KnockoutJS

Git

Java

Unix

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

Business Analysis

Requirements Analysis

Software Project Management

SQL

COBOL

Requirements Gathering

Software Development

Management

Integration

Certifications

Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree

Udacity April 2015

Website Performance Optimization

Udacity February 2015

Object-Oriented Javascript

Udacity January 2015

JavaScript Basics

Udacity December 2014

Intro to HTML and CSS

Udacity October 2014

The Data Scientist's Toolbox

Coursera May 2014

Programming Mobile Applications for Android Handheld Systems

Coursera March 2014

Startup Engineering

Coursera September 2013

Developing Innovative Ideas for New Companies: The First Step in Entrepreneurship

Coursera July 2013

DB2 9 for Z/OS Database Administration

IBM February 2012

Education

Udacity

Nanodegree, Front-end Web Development, 2014 - 2015

University of Sto. Tomas

Bachelor of Science in Math Major in Computer Science, 1993 - 1997

Languages

English

Filipino

Normandy Real

Frontend Developer, Database Administrator

normandy.real@gmail.com



Contact Normandy on LinkedIn